<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<product>
	<data>
		<title>American Lifting Electric Palletizer Tables - 24" x 48" </title>
		<meta-title>Used Carl Stahl American Lifting Air-Actuated Electric Palletizer Tables - 24" x 48" | American Surplus - America's #1 Used Material Handling Equipment Dealer</meta-title>
		<meta-description>Used Carl Stahl American Lifting Palletizer Tables are For Sale at American Surplus. Featuring a 24" x 48"  platform,  4,500 lb. lift capacity, 10-35" travel height, and air actuation instead of hydraulics. They're in stock and available for nationwide shipping at up to 60% off the cost of new! Learn more about our Electric Air-Actuated Palletizer Tables and other used lift tables online at americansurplus.com</meta-description>
		<product-code>196</product-code>
		<pricing>
			<list-price></list-price>
			<asi-price>2595.00</asi-price>
			<as-low-as-price></as-low-as-price>
		</pricing>
		<related>
			<1>195</1>
			<2>198</2>
			<3>199</3>
			<4>197</4>
		</related>
		<category>
			<name>Used Lift Tables</name>
			<priority>1000</priority>
		</category>
		<site-presence>
			<backorder>0</backorder> <!-- 1 = true, 0 = false -->
			<is-visible>1</is-visible> <!-- 1 = true, 0 = false -->
		</site-presence>
		<attributes>
			<attribute>
				<name>Brand</name>
				<value>Carl Stahl American Lifting</value>
			</attribute>
			<attribute>
				<name>Travel Range</name>
				<value>10-35"</value>
			</attribute>
			<attribute>
				<name>Capacity</name>
				<value>4,500 lbs.</value>
			</attribute>
			<attribute>
				<name>Lift Table Platform Size</name>
				<value>24" x 48"</value>
			</attribute>
			<attribute>
				<name>Operation</name>
				<value>Air-Actuated</value>
			</attribute>
			<attribute>
				<name>Controls</name>
				<value>Foot-Pedal Control</value>
			</attribute>
		</attributes>
		<images> <!-- Include all pictures on the page, in both gallery and body. -->
			<image>
				<name>IMG_0444.JPG</name>
				<placement>gallery</placement> <!-- gallery or body -->
				<is-primary>1</is-primary> <!-- 1 = true, 0 = false, blank on body pictures -->
				<priority>1</priority> <!-- blank on body pictures -->
				<alt></alt>
			</image>
		</images>
	</data>
	<content>
		<extra-short-description>
			<ul>
				<li>Platform Size: 24" x 48"</li>
				<li>Air-Actuated</li>
				<li>4,500 lb. capacity</li>
			</ul>
		</extra-short-description>
		<short-description>
			<ul>
				<li>Durable steel lifting arms allow for off-center loading up to 50%</li>
				<li>Easily installs and operates with your current air system - No hydraulics!</li>
				<li>Easily adjustable for loads between 1,000 and 4,500 lbs.</li>
			</ul>
		</short-description>
		<long-description>
			<p>The ABP Air Actuated Electric Palletizer by Carl Stahl American Lifting are available used at American Surplus! These palletizers both operate and install easily; just hook them up to your current air system, set your desired pressure to determine load height, and you're ready to go! An easy to use foot switch allows you to control your load level for quick loading and height adjustment. Your choice to add an air-actuated palletizer or other type of <a href="https://www.americansurplus.com/used-equipment/used-lift-equipment/used-lift-tables/">lift table</a> allows your staff to quickly and efficiently palletize loads while minimizing bending, reducing worker fatigue. These American Lifting Palletizer are capable of handling loads from 1,000 to 4,500 lbs, ensuring that it can handle a wide array of challenges you choose to throw at it.</p>
			<p style="color: red;"><strong>We can&rsquo;t list our entire inventory online, if you do not see what you are looking for, just ask! Quantity discounts available on used lift tables 40-60% off the price of new. Call 800-876-3736 for additional information &amp; a free quote. American Surplus will provide a quote on new equipment if used is unavailable. Nationwide shipping is available. Price and product availability subject to change without notice. Inventory is subject to prior sale.</strong></p>
		</long-description>
	</content>
</product>